{
    "id": "32e7fb5ff7ff4787816aaa1bcd1e9e58",
    "title": "Gap Fills Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Moments later the sun disappeared …………………. the horizon.",
            "description": "We prefer below when one thing is not directly under another.",
            "answers": [
                "under",
                "underneath",
                "below"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "9dc9aaeb7576422da0167b80bd859348"
        },
        {
            "question": "We ……………………….. at six while the roads were empty.",
            "description": "We do not use begin to talk about starting a journey.",
            "answers": [
                "began",
                "started",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "fd49da60b25f4711b989683f363ae97c"
        },
        {
            "question": "You are still …………………………",
            "description": "Underneath can only indicate physical position.",
            "answers": [
                "below",
                "under",
                "underneath"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "084d78ca46824782b392d255164dfd9a"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………. three suspects have been arrested.",
            "description": "We can use either all or all the before a number.",
            "answers": [
                "All",
                "All the",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "d9b6fbe276fe449abffb6c0a993ebb04"
        },
        {
            "question": "We spend ………………………… weekends at our country cottage.",
            "description": "Alternate means every second.",
            "answers": [
                "alternate",
                "alternative",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f89830816dd84ebc9f15b94534b0c9c0"
        },
        {
            "question": "It looks ……………………….. it’s going to rain.",
            "description": "Like is possible here in an informal style.",
            "answers": [
                "like",
                "as if",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "931ec99b5f934cebb83d97051fa99c7e"
        },
        {
            "question": "It is important that she ………………………. told.",
            "description": "In British English, should is used before be in this structure. The structure without should is more common in American English.",
            "answers": [
                "be",
                "should be",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "7442bedcec744e07b08ae31a00baaad4"
        },
        {
            "question": "I would like two dozen mangoes ………………………..",
            "description": "Altogether can be used to give totals.",
            "answers": [
                "all together",
                "altogether"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8203feb61811446fbb46e40d6688801b"
        },
        {
            "question": "The committee …………………………. announced its decision.",
            "description": "Committee is a collective noun. In American English, collective nouns are always treated as singular. ",
            "answers": [
                "has",
                "have",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "09fdcf9ba69b4ec4ad79542e3801c150"
        },
        {
            "question": "I will telephone you after I ……………………….",
            "description": "When the verb in the main clause is in the future tense, we use a present tense in the subordinate clause to refer to future.",
            "answers": [
                "arrive",
                "will arrive",
                "would arrive"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "fa42d65c9828404ca744d1d0711b4f07"
        },
        {
            "question": "Martha is a/an ……………………………. woman.",
            "description": "Afraid is not usually used before a noun in attributive position.",
            "answers": [
                "afraid",
                "frightened",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0e7a2b3092904efba97b06bad4952851"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am going to do my exams, and ………………………. I’m going to study law.",
            "description": "After is not used alone as an adverb. Instead we use afterwards. ",
            "answers": [
                "after",
                "afterwards",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "db5ca443c7ce43069fe1f5471cfded37"
        }
    ]
}